<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Leaf.Guide</title>
    <link>https://leaf.guide/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Leaf.Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 08:25:02 +0930</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leaf.guide/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stremio &#43; Real-Debrid</title>
      <link>https://leaf.guide/posts/stremio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 08:25:02 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leaf.guide/posts/stremio/</guid>
      <description>Stremio is an app that when paired with Real-Debrid, allows you to stream almost any movie or tv show in high quality.
Real Debrid costs money but it is inexpensive and allows for much faster streaming speeds as aposed to streaming torrents. No VPN is needed to use RD as it is all through DDL. It torrents movies for you and puts them on their servers which is where you stream them from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recomended Tools</title>
      <link>https://leaf.guide/posts/recommended_tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 15:18:12 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leaf.guide/posts/recommended_tools/</guid>
      <description>This guide will only list basic tools which are commonly needed for sailing the seas.
There are much bigger lists out there for useful tools however this guide will not list every single useful tool in order to keep it simple and easy to read. This keeps it from being overwhelming and confusing for new users.
Torrents - qbittorrent For torrenting qbittorrent is the most commonly recommended. It is open source and light weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11</title>
      <link>https://leaf.guide/posts/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 15:18:12 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leaf.guide/posts/windows/</guid>
      <description>Installing Windows IoT Enterprise LTS version from a USB.
You will need an empty USB with at least 8gb of storage
Step 1: Making a bootable USB Download the Windows 11 IoT Enterprise LTSC .iso from MassGrave The IoT Enterprise LTSC is a version of Windows that doesn&amp;rsquo;t include any bloatware and has far fewer updates by only giving the needed security ones.
Download and run Balena Etcher Select the Windows .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
